{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "a city\n\n---> six ___",
      "answer": "cities",
      "explain": "\n\n- city -> cities\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nose \n\n---> seven ___ ",
      "answer": "noses",
      "explain": "\n\n- nose -> noses",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bag \n\n---> five ___ ",
      "answer": "bags",
      "explain": "\n\n- bag -> bags",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a buffalo\n\n---> two ___\n",
      "answer": "buffaloes",
      "explain": "\n\n- buffalo -> buffaloes\nMost nouns ending in o preceded by a consonant -> +es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a name \n\n---> six ___ ",
      "answer": "names",
      "explain": "\n\n- name -> names",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a girl \n\n---> ten ___ ",
      "answer": "girls",
      "explain": "\n\n- girl -> girls",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pony\n\n---> two ___",
      "answer": "ponies",
      "explain": "\n\n- pony -> ponies\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pencil \n\n---> eight ___ ",
      "answer": "pencils",
      "explain": "\n\n- pencil -> pencils",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a baby \n\n---> four ___ ",
      "answer": "babies",
      "explain": "\n\n- baby -> babies\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lady\n\n---> ten ___",
      "answer": "ladies",
      "explain": "\n\n- lady -> ladies\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "4"
    }
  ]
}